Finding Aid for Claude Halstead Van Tyne papers, 1885-1930
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Professional and Personal Papers
  - War Aims Lectures taught to Student Army Training Corps at the University of Michigan 1917
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
Oct. 24, 1919, Jan. 19, 1923, Oct. 19, 1923, Oct. 31, 1923, Jan. 2, 1924, Mar. 10, 1925, July 24, 1925, Nov. 18, 1926, Jan. 31, 1929.
Fox, Dixon Ryan, 1887-1945.
Dec. 12, 1923, Oct. 22, 1924.
Frayer, William Alley.
Feb. 25, 1912, Sept. 2, 1912, Jan. 26, 1914, Dec. 5, 1914, Mar. 4, 1915, Aug. 5, 1917.
Frédéricq, Paul, 1850-1920.
June ?, 1910.
Garfield, Harry Augustus, 1863-1942.
May 1, 1922, May 31, 1922, June 28, 1922, Aug. 10, 1925.
Garner, James Wilford, 1871-1938.
May 17, 1922.
Gay, Edwin F. (Edwin Francis), 1867-1946.
Jan. 15, 1919, July 12, 1922, July 26, 1922, Sept. 26, 1923.
Gipson, Lawrence Henry, 1880-
Dec. 14, 1918.
Gore, Victor M.
Dec. 31, 1924.
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
Dec. 20, 1928.
Greene, Evarts Boutell, 1870-1947.
Feb. 25, 1908, Mar. 3, 1908, Oct. 24, 1908, Jan. 6, 1909, Feb. 24, 1910, Mar. 13, 1911, Oct. 8, 1911, Nov. 2, 1914, May 6, 1918, Sept. 25, 1918, May 24, 1923, Dec. 17, 1925, Feb. 6, 1928, Jan. 4, 1929, Jan. 7, 1929, Jan. 9, 1929, Feb. 1, 1929.
Haigh, Henry A. (Henry Allyn), b. 1854.
Dec. 19, 1920, Apr. 20, 1925, Dec. 10, 1925, Dec. 16, 1926, Dec. 24, 1925.
Hanchett, Benjamin Sawtell, 1868-1933.
July 29, 1925.
Harris, Thomas L. (Thomas Le Grand), 1863-1941.
June 18, 1910.
Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1854-1943.
May 30, 1885, Dec. 5, 1902, Dec. 13, 1902, Dec. 20, 1902, Sept. 21, 1903, Nov. 30, 1903, Jan. 13, 1904, May 4, 1904, May 9, 1904, May 12, 1904, June 1, 1904, June 3, 1904, Oct. 19, 1904, Oct. 21, 1904, Dec. 5, 1904, Dec. 17, 1904
Jan. 4, 1905, Jan. 7, 1905, Feb. 2, 1905, Feb. 20, 1905, Mar. 31, 1905, May 3, 1905, May 17, 1905, Jan. 19, 1907, Jan. 21, 1907, Feb. 6, 1907, May 8, 1908, May 18, 1908, Apr. 22, 1910, June 2, 1911, Oct. 12, 1911, Apr. 6, 1925, Jan. 19, 1927, Sept. 12, 1947.
Haskins, Charles Homer, 1870-1937.
Oct. 2, 1906, Jan. 13, 1908, Oct. 10, 1908, Oct. 31, 1911, Oct. 31, 1911, Apr. 11, 1912, Nov. 1, 1912, Feb. 18, 1914, Mar. 20, 1925, May 2, 1925, May 15, 1925.
Hayes, Carlton Joseph Huntley, 1882-1964.
Dec. 1, 1925, Apr. 27, 1926.
Hill, Arthur, 1847-1909.
July 5, 1907.
Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1952.
Jan. 14, 1914, June 12, 1914, July 12, 1917, Jan. 9, 1918, Jan. 22, 1918, Feb. 1, 1918, Sept. 1, 1918, Aug. 9, 1919, Jan. 9, 1920, Nov. 20, 1927, Aug. 11, 1912.
Hodder, Frank Heywood, 1860-1935
Dec. 7, 1917, Sept. 28, 1924, Oct. 15, 1924, Nov. 2, 1924, Jan. 15, 1925.
Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951.
Mar. 13, 1926.
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.
Sept. 24, Oct. 16, 1914 [folder no. 37]
Hubbard, Lucius L. (Lucius Lee), 1849-1933
May 7, 1912.
Huber, Gotthelf Carl, 1865-1934.
Jan. 17, 1930.
Hull, Charles Henry, b. 1864.
Jan. 19, 1907, Feb. 29, 1908, May 14, 1908, Dec. 5, 1908, May 26, 1910, Apr. 14, 1917.
Hulst, Cornelia Steketee, 1865-1957.
Sept. 25, 1922, Dec. 4, 1924, Jan. 26, 1925, Oct. 4, 1925, Oct. 16, 1925.
Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.
Nov. 5, 1907, Jan. 4, 1911, Feb. 17, 1911, Mar. 19, 1911, June 7, 1913, Dec. 16, 1913, Jan. 7, 1914, Aug. 5, 1918, Aug. 16, 1918, Sept. 12, 1918, Sept. 14, 1918, Jan. 11, 1919.
Hyma, Albert, 1893-
June 23, 1922, Mar. 5, 1923, Apr. 24, 1924, May 3, 1926, Dec. 31, 1928.
Jameson, J. Franklin (John Franklin), 1859-1937.
Jan. 10, 1922, Oct. 16, 1903, Apr. 28, 1904, May 17, 1904, June 6, 1904, June 21, 1904, Oct. 14, 1904, Oct. 29, 1904, Nov. 4, 1904, Nov. 13, 1904, Feb. 7, 1905, Mar. 26, 1905, Apr. 4, 1905, Apr. 18, 1905
Jan. 3, 1907, Jan. 14, 1907, Jan. 21, 1907, Feb. 7, 1907, Oct. 1, 1907, Jan. 6, 1908, May 11, 1908, May 21, 1908, Oct. 15, 1908, Jan. 14, 1909, Mar. 12, 1909, Nov. 8, 1909, Mar. 28, 1910, Apr. 4, 1910, Apr. 19, 1910, Mar. 20, 1910, May 16, 1910
Feb. 8, 1911, May 1, 1911, Apr. 1, 1912, Oct. 14, 1912, Jan. 9, 1914, Mar. 28, 1914, Dec. 13, 1916, Aug. 3, 1917, Mar. 5, 1918, Mar. 8, 1918, Apr. 19, 1918, Aug. 6, 1918, Dec. 3, 1918, Dec. 12, 1918, Mar. 10, 1919, July 26, 1919, Mar. 5, 1920
Aug. 25, 1921, July 10, 1922, Oct. 4, 1922, Feb. 27, 1923, Mar. 16, 1923, May 23, 1923, Feb. 9, 1924, Mar. 1, 1924, Sept. 15, 1924, Sept. 29, 1924, Jan. 7, 1925, Jan. 20, 1925, Mar. 10, 1925, Mar. 18, 1925, Mar. 28, 1925, July 18, 1925, May 26, 1926, Aug. 16, 1926, Nov. 9, 1927, May 15, 1928, May 6, 1929.
Jastrow, Morris, 1861-1921.
Feb. 28, 1907.
Jenks, William Lee, 1856-1936.
May 3, 1916, Nov. 4, 1921.
Kelley, Patrick Henry, 1867-1925.
June 2, 1921.
Kelsey, Francis W. (Francis Willey), b. 1858.
Mar. 4, 1911, May 24, 1924.
King, Clyde Lyndon, 1879-1937.
Dec. 11, 1909, Apr. 10, 1910, Nov. 29, 1926
Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.
May 1, 1907, Jan. 27, 1908, May 26, 1908.
Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941.
Mar. 28, 1910, Dec. 27, 1913.
Kraus, Edward Henry, 1875-
Nov. 4, 1912, Dec. 10, 1926, Sept. 29, 1927.
Lane, Robert Porter, 1891-1953.
Dec. 18, 1911, Aug. 9, 1917, Sept. 6, 1917.
Langer, William L. (William Leonard), 1896-1977.
Jan. 15, 1929.
Larson, Laurence Marcellus, 1868-1938.
Feb. 27, 1923.
Latane, John Holladay, 1869-1932.
Nov. 29, 1911, Dec. 8, 1911, Jan. 17, 1912, Jan. 23, 1912, Feb. 12, 1912, May 8, 1912, May 23, 1912.
Leland, Frank Bruce.
May 23, 1916.
LeRoy, James A. (James Alfred), 1875-1909.
May 25, 1906.
Little, Clarence C. (Clarence Cook), b. 1888.
Oct. 5, 1925, Nov. 30, 1925, Feb. 15, 1926, Apr. 27, 1926.
Lloyd, Alfred H. (Alfred Henry), 1864-1927.
Sept. 11, 1911, Dec. 19, 1918, July 2, 1925, July 17, 1925, Oct. 25, 1926, Dec. 17, 1926, Oct. 5, 1926.
Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1850-1924.
Sept. 27, 1918, Jan. 28, 1919.
Loud, Edward F.
May 30, 1908.
Loud, George Alvin, 1852-1925.
Dec. 3, 1907, Dec. 22, 1909, Apr. 15, 1916, May 24, 1916.
Lovejoy, P. S., 1884-1942.
May 27, 1914, June 25, 1914.
Lucas, Henry Stephen, 1889-1961.
Feb. 24, 1926, Mar. 31, 1926, Nov. 5, 1928.
McClure, Harry H.
Nov. 18, 1903, Dec. 1, 1903, Aug. 15, 1905, Aug. 4, 1908, Jan. 23, 1909, Feb. 11, 1909.
McGregor, Tracy William, 1869-1936.
Sept. 23, 1925.
Mackenzie, William Dexter, 1873-1960.
May 27, 1926.
McLaren, Walter Wallace.
June 6, 1922.
McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham, 1861-1947.
5 undated letters, Dec. 19, 1902, Jan. 8, 1903, Feb. 5, 1903, Mar. -, 1903, Mar. 9, 1903, May 15, 1903, Jan. 10, 1904, Jan. 13, 1904, Mar. 10, 1904, Mar. 22, 1904, Apr. 5, 1904, Apr. 11, 1904, May 9, 1904, May 12, 1904, Sept. 23, 1904, Oct. 19, 1904, Nov. 12, 1904
Jan. 10, 1905, Jan. 18, 1905, Jan. 20, 1905, Feb. 1, 1905, Feb. 6, 1905, Feb. 20, 1905, Mar. 6, 1905, Mar. 15, 1905, Mar. 16, 1905, Mar. 17, 1905, Mar. 20, 1905, Mar. 27, 1905, Apr. 12, 1905, May 4, 1905, May 4, 1905, May 9, 1905, May 29, 1905, June 4, 1905, Aug. 24, 1905
Mar. 13, 1907, Apr. 11, 1907, Aug. 3, 1907, Oct. 28, 1907, Nov. 7, 1907, Jan. 10, 1908, Jan. 22, 1908, Mar. 24, 1908, Mar. 7, 1908, Apr. 1, 1908, May 11, 1908, Aug. 24, 1908, Mar. 8, 1909, Oct. 13, 1909, Oct. 30, 1909, Dec. 28, 1909
Jan. 6, 1910, Feb. 2, 1910, June 9, 1910, Oct. 6, 1910, June 21, 1911, Aug. 7, 1911, Oct. 4, 1911, Oct. 25, 1911, Dec. 16, 1911, Jan. 23, 1912, Apr. 3, 1912, Apr. 24, 1912, Apr. 29, 1912, May 8, 1912, June 13, 1912
May 25, 1913, May 30, 1913, July 14, 1913, July 21, 1913, Aug. 21, 1913, Oct. 14, 1913, Nov. 3, 1913, Nov. 17, 1913, Nov. 26, 1913, Feb. 30, 1914, May 5, 1914, June 29, 1914, Nov. 4, 1914
Feb. 9, 1915, May 15, 1915, June 3, 1915, July 3, 1915, Oct. 18, 1915, Nov. 7, 1915, Dec. 15, 1915, Dec. 22, 1915, Jan. 25, 1916, Feb. 5, 1916, Nov. 4, 1916
Feb. 16, 1917, Mar. 8, 1917, May 10, 1917, Nov. 7, 1917, Nov. 9, 1917, Nov. 14, 1917, Nov. 19, 1917, Nov. 27, 1917, Jan. 6, 1918, Mar. 28, 1918, Apr. 15, 1918, Oct. 7, 1918, Nov. 5, 1918, Jan. 23, 1919, May 8, 1919, Oct. 6, 1919
Jan. 14, 1920, Oct. 5, 1920, Sept. 29, 1921, Oct. 18, 1921, Jan. 6, 1922, Jan. 12, 1922, Oct. 6, 1922, Dec. 20, 1922, Dec. 27, 1922, Sept. 20, 1923, Nov. 9, 1923, Jan. 3, 1924, Jan. 8, 1924, Dec. 8, 1925, Apr. 6, 1926, Apr. 29, 1926, May 6, 1926, Nov. 15, 1929, Nov. 22, 1929.
Malcolm, George A. (George Arthur), 1881-1961
Mar. 4, 1908, May 14, 1912, Nov. 7, 1916, July 3, 1922.
Meany, Edmond S. (Edmond Stephen), 1862-1935.
Dec. 8, 1925.
Miller, Edwin Lillie, 1868-1934.
Sept. 20, 1928, Sept. 27, 1928, Sept. 29, 1928.
Millspaugh, Arthur Chester, 1883-1955.
Jan. 12, 1910.
Moore, Charles, 1855-1942.
May 11, 1910, July 7, 1915, Oct. 13, 1915, Jan. 31, 1916.
More, Paul Elmer, 1864-1937.
Mar. 7, 1903, Apr. 10, 1903, Aug. 13, 1903, Aug. 28, 1903, Oct. 15, 1904, Apr. 12, 1910, May 5, 1910, Oct. 16, 1913.
Morison, Samuel Eliot, 1887-1976.
June 29, 1925.
Muir, Ramsay, 1872-1941.
Dec. 26, 1927.
Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.
Nov. 3, 1921, Dec. 20, 1924.
Myers, Albert Cook, 1874-1960.
Mar. 26, 1911, May 16, 1912.
Nearing, Scott, 1883-
May 24, 1916.
Nevins, Allan, 1890-1971.
Oct. 13, 1924.
North, Lucian Gregory, 1850-1925.
Dec. 9, 1904, Dec. 21, 1904, Jan. 4, 1906.
Notestein, Wallace, 1878-1969.
Nov. 25, 1926.
Oberholtzer, Ellis Paxson, 1868-1936.
Nov. 17, 1903, Nov. 27, 1903, Dec. 9, 1903, Dec. 11, 1903, Dec. 19, 1903, Dec. 29, 1903, Jan. 3, 1904, Jan. 13, 1904, Jan. 28, 1904, Sept. 16, 1905, Oct. 10, 1905, Jan. 4, 1906, Jan. 16, 1906, Jan. 14, 1910, Jan. 26, 1910.
Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860
Apr. 7, 1911.
Pattengill, Henry Romaine, 1852-1918.
Nov. 4, 1904, Feb. 5, 1916.
Patterson, John C., 1838-1910.
Apr. 28, 1910.
Paxson, Frederic L. (Frederic Logan), 1877-1948.
Feb. -, 1903, Jan. 14, 1904, May 16, 1904, Mar. 17, 1905, Oct. 22, 1905, Apr. 17, 1906, May 4, 1906, July 29, 1907, Dec. 13, 1910, Mar. 1, 1911, Mar. 13, 1911, Mar. 21, 1911, May 19, 1911, May 24, 1911, June 19, 1911, Aug. 11, 1911, Aug. 14, 1911, Dec. 13, 1911
Feb. 3, 1912, Apr. 28, 1912, May 9, 1912, May 28, 1912, Sept. 24, 1912, Oct. 26, 1913, Nov. 26, 1913, Aug. 29, 1914, Nov. 11, 1914, Nov. 15, 1914, Feb. 7, 1915, Oct. 16, 1915, Oct. 20, 1915
Apr. 22, 1918, May 3, 1918, Nov. 21, 1919, May 26, 1920, Oct. 27, 1921, Nov. 3, 1921, July 20, 1922, July 9, 1923, Mar. 10, 1925, Mar. 19, 1929, Mar. 22, 1929.
Pearson, Karl G.
Dec. 23, 1921.
Pease, Theodore Calvin, 1887-1948.
Oct. 3, 1927.
Pelzer, Louis, 1879-1946.
Feb. 24, 1925.
Perry, Maude Elaine Caldwell, 1873-1963
Dec. ?, 1917.
Perry, Stuart Hoffman, 1874-1957.
Apr. 18, 1916, Apr. 20, 1916, May 5, 1916, Dec. 18, 1917, Dec. 26, 1918, Sept. 19, 1922, Oct. 2, 1922, Mar. 3, 1923, Mar. 4, 1923, Oct. 3, 1923, Nov. 28, 1928, Dec. 3, 1928, Jan. 3, 1929.
Phillips, Ulrich Bonnell, 1877-1934.
May 3, 1902, Feb. 1, 1907, Feb. 23, 1907, Mar. 3, 1907, Jan. 29, 1911, Feb. 7, 1911, Feb. 24, 1911, Mar. 12, 1911, Apr. 1, 1911, Apr. 26, 1911, June 12, 1911, June 18, 1911, July 7, 1911, July 15, 1911, July 21, 1911, July 24, 1911, Aug. 26, 1911, July 11, 1912, Aug. 3, 1912, July 12, 1913, Oct. 23, 1913, Oct. 26, 1913, Feb. 15, 1914
Nov. 4, 1917, Nov. 17, 1917, Dec. 20, 1917, Jan. 1, 1918, Jan. 16, 1918, Nov. 19, 1918, Nov. 23, 1918, Dec. 19, 1918, Jan. 4, 1919, Feb. 4, 1920, Jan. 30, 1924, May 25, 1924, June 11, 1925, May 15, 1927, Nov. 27, 1928, Aug. 8, 1929, Nov. 14, 1929, July 31, 1914 [folder no. 37]
Pierce, Bessie Louise, 1888-1974.
Feb. 18, 1928.
Pollock, James Kerr, 1898-
Aug. 15, 1927.
Potter, William W., 1869-1940.
Oct. 26, 1918.
Pound, Arthur, 1884-1966.
Sept. 8, 1906, Oct. 3, 1907, Mar. 1, 1909, Mar. 11, 1909, May 13, 1911, Nov. 18, 1918, Dec. 2, 1918, Oct. 5, 1921, Oct. 27, 1921, Nov. 2, 1921, Apr. 5, 1922, Feb. 28, 1923, Apr. 9, 1926, Jan. 10, 1929, Feb. 4, 1929, Feb. 19, 1929, Mar. 2, 1929.
Priestley, Herbert Ingram, 1875-1944.
Nov. 12, 1927, Dec. 6, 1927.
Putnam, George Haven, 1844-1930.
Sept. 8, 1915, May 11, 1927.
Putnam, Herbert, 1861-1955.
Jan. 5, 1903, July 4, 1903, July 8, 1903, Nov. 21, 1904, Dec. 10, 1904, Dec. 17, 1904, Mar. 8, 1905, May 17, 1906, Oct. 2, 1906, Oct. 6, 1906.
Rand, Benjamin, 1856-1934.
Dec. 16, 1902, Jan. 26, 1903.
Randall, J. G. (James Garfield), 1881-1953.
Dec. 15, 1909, Apr. 25, 1911, May 22, 1911, May 30, 1911, Sept. 22, 1912.
Rankin, Thomas Ernest, 1872-1953.
Feb. 21, 1922.
Rebec, George, 1868-1944.
May 11, 1912, Nov. 14, 1925, Apr. 28, 1926.
Reeves, Jesse Siddall, 1872-
May 6, 1910, Dec. 13, 1913, Feb. 23, 1914, Mar. 14, 1914, Feb. 8, 1918, Dec. 15, 1921, Mar. 3, 1922, Oct. 22, 1925.
Riggs, Henry Earle, b. 1865.
Dec. 26, 1922.
Robbins, Frank Egleston, 1884-
Nov. 3, 1921, Mar. 24, 1925, Mar. 19, 1925, Mar. 31, 1925, Sept. 9, 1928, Nov. 30, 1928, Feb. 23, 1929, Mar. 15, 1929.
Robertson, James Alexander, 1873-1939.
Jan. 1, 1923.
Robinson, Edgar Eugene, 1887-
Aug. 13, 1925.
Robinson, James Harvey, 1863-1936.
Apr. 29, 1906.
Rolfe, John Carew, 1859-1943.
Mar. 14, 1903, Apr. 12, 1903.
Rose, John Holland, 1855-1942.
Nov. 17, 1927, Dec. 22, 1927.
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-
Oct. 23, 1929, Dec. 21, 1929.
Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.
July 1, 1909, Dec. 23, 1924, Feb. 11, 1929, Jan. 7, 1930.
Schelling, Felix Emmanuel, 1858-1945.
Mar. 14, 1902, Nov. 6, 1903, Dec. 9, 1904, Apr. 25, 1905, Sept. 27, 1905, Mar. 23, 1906, May 24, 1906, Sept. 2, 1907, Feb. 28, 1908, Apr. 8, 1908, Apr. 14, 1908, May 11, 1908, Dec. 16, 1908, Nov. 15, 1909
Jan. 30, 1912, Feb. 8, 1912, Feb. 23, 1912, Feb. 24, 1912, Mar. 2, 1912, Mar. 9, 1912, Mar. 29, 1912, Apr. 11, 1912, May 7, 1912, May 31, 1912, Nov. 2, 1912, Oct. 24, 1914, Nov. 6, 1914, Dec. 18, 1914
Apr. 27, 1915, Apr. 29, 1915, May 9, 1915, Dec. 22, 1916, Jan. 22, 1918, Apr. 7, 1919, Oct. 2, 1920, Feb. 28, 1922, July 14, 1922, Oct. 26, 1922, Nov. 30, 1922, Dec. 6, 1922.
Schevill, Ferdinand, 1868-1954.
Sept. 26, 1925.
Schlesinger, Arthur Meier, 1888-1965.
Jan. 15, 1916, Sept. 26, 1921, Nov. 3, 1923, Nov. 8, 1923, Dec. 12, 1923, Mar. 28, 1924, Apr. 14, 1926.
Scribner, Charles, 1854-1930.
Jan. 28, 1915.
Seligman, Edwin Robert Anderson, 1861-1939.
Oct. 3, 1922.
Sellery, George C. (George Clarke), 1872-
Mar. 12, 1912.
Shorts, Robert Perry, 1879-
Jan. 16, 1930.
Shotwell, Ambrose Milton, 1853-
July 29, 1909.
Shotwell, James Thomson, 1874-1965.
Apr. 5, 1917.
Siebert, Wilbur Henry, 1866-1961.
Dec. 6, 1928.
Sioussat, St. George L. (St. George Leakin), 1878-1960.
Dec. 8, 1909, Jan. 23, 1908, May 24, 1924.
Slosson, Edwin Emery, 1865-1929.
Oct. 1, 1904, Oct. 6, 1904, Nov. 10, 1904, Nov. 14, 1904, Nov. 19, 1904, Nov. 20, 1904, Dec. 12, 1904, Dec. 15, 1904, Dec. 22, 1904, Dec. 23, 1904, Dec. 27, 1904, Jan. 4, 1905, Feb. 28, 1905, Apr. 26, 1905, Aug. 23, 1912, Nov. 10, 1913, June 9, 1921, June 21, 1921, Mar. 21, 1924.
Slosson, Preston W. (Preston William), 1892-
June 21, 1921, Mar. 21, 1924, Mar. 28, 1924, May 11, 1925, June 12, 1927.
Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.
Apr. 18, 1899, May 9, 1899, Jan. 13, 1907, Sept. 9, 1907, Sept. 22, 1907, July 26, 1908, May 24, 1909, Apr. 18, 1910, May 31, 1911, Feb. 1, 1912, Nov. 19, 1912, Apr. 18, 1918, Oct. 31, 1921, Mar. 5, 1925, Mar. 20, 1925, Dec. 14, 1925, Feb. 1, 1926, Oct. 24, 1928
Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.
Feb. 18, 1917, Sept. 19, 1918, Nov. 19, 1917.
Spaulding, Mr. (Oliver Lyman), 1833-1922.
Mar. 11, 1928.
Stephenson, Wendell Holmes, 1899-1970.
Mar. 21, 1926.
Stone, Ralph, 1868-1956.
Dec. 22, 1924.
Sweet, William Warren, 1881-1959.
Mar. 28, 1918.
Swinton, Roy Stanley, 1886-
Apr. 18, 1911.
Tarbell, Ida M. (Ida Minerva), 1857-1944.
Oct. 25, 1904, Aug. 2, 1905, Feb. 22, 1909, Feb. 5, 1909, Apr. 13, 1909, Aug. 21, 1916.
Tatlock, John S. P. (John Strong Perry), 1876-1948.
Sept. 11, 1903, Aug. 5, 1912, July 2, 1913, Oct. 1, 1913, Dec. 15, 1913, Mar. 26, 1914, Oct. 14, 1915, Jan. 17, 1916, Sept. 15, 1917, Sept. 24, 1919, May 16, 1920, Dec. 14, 1920, May 2, 1925, June 12, 1926, Mar. 16, 1928, Jan. 27, 1939.
Teggart, Frederick John, 1870-1946.
May 13, 1915.
Thayer, William Roscoe, 1859-1923.
Undated.
Thompson, James Westfall, 1869-1941.
Mar. 12, 1924.
Thwaites, Reuben Gold, 1853-1913.
Oct. 28, 1907, Nov. 4, 1907.
Trevelyan, George Macaulay, 1876-1962.
Correspondence [folder 54].
Trevelyan, George Otto, Sir, bart., 1838-1928.
Correspondence, 1912-1927 [folders 52-53].
Turner, Edward Raymond, 1881-1929.
Feb. 3, 1911, Feb. 12, 1911, Feb. 18, 1911, Feb. 19, 1911, Mar. 9, 1911, Mar. 15, 1911, Mar. 23, 1911, Mar. 23, 1911, ca. Apr. 3, 1911, Apr. 3, 1911, Apr. 5, 1911, Apr. 7, 1911, Apr. 14, 1911, Apr. 27, 1911, May 6, 1911, May 8, 1911, May 11, 1911, Summer, 1911, Summer, 1911, Sept. 10, 1911, ca. Sept. -, 1911
Mar. 19, 1912, June 1, 1912, Sept. 30, 1912, Jan. 27, 1913, July 26, 1913, Oct. 17, 1913, Nov. 21, 1913, Dec. 15, 1913, Mar. 17, 1914, June 1, 1914, Aug. 20, 1914, Aug. 24, 1914, Aug. 25, 1914, Aug. 29, 1914, Sept. -, 1914
Apr. 26, 1918, July 28, 1918, Aug. 11, 1918, June 28, 1921, Aug. 20, 1921, Sept. 12, 1921, Feb. 11, 1922, Mar. 18, 1922, May 21, 1922, Dec. 8, 1922, Feb. 13, 1924, Oct. 23, 1924, Nov. 18, 1924, five undated letters ca. 1925, May 29, 1925, Oct. 3, 1925, Oct. 15, 1925, Dec. 15, 1925
Nov. 12, 1926, Jan. 7, 1927, Aug. 23, 1927, Oct. 28, 1927, Dec. 8, 1927, Feb. 15, 1928, May 10, 1928, May 23, 1928, Oct. 18, 1928, May 13, 1929, Nov. 17, 1929, last page of letter (no date) to B.L. Richmond, The Times Literary Supplement, London.
Turner, Frederick Jackson, 1861-1932.
Sept. 14, 1903, Oct. 9, 1903, Oct. 17, 1903, Nov. 10, 1903, Aug. 30, 1904, Mar. 31, 1905 [folder 34], Apr. 21, 1905 [folder 34] and Dec. 21, 1905 [folder 34], Jan. 12, 1906, July 14, 1906, June 1, 1907, Dec. 24, 1907, Feb. 26, 1908, Mar. 2, 1908, Apr. 21, 1908 [folder 35] and April 25, 1908 [folder 35], June 15, 1908
Apr. 24, 1909, Dec. 3, 1909, Jan. 31, 1910, Apr. 11, 1910, May 8, 1910, Feb. 24, 1911, Apr. 15, 1911, Oct.13, 1911, June 2, 1912, Jan. 8, 1915 [folder 37], Aug. 15, 1915 [folder 37], Jan. 2, 1916, Jan. 15, 1916 [folder 38], May 11, 1917, May 11, 1917, Nov. 2, 1917, Nov. 1, 1921 [folder 43], May 8, 1922, July 12, 1922 [folder 44], Oct. 2, 1922, Dec. 11, 1925.
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
July 27, 1925, Apr. 15, 1929, Nov. 12, 1920.
Vander Velde, Lewis G. (Lewis George), 1890-1975.
May 15, 1926, June 14, 1926, Mar. 10, 1927, Apr. 30, 1928.
Waldo, Dwight Bryant, 1864-1939.
May 28, 1909.
Walker, Williston, 1860-1922.
Oct. 17, 1920.
Weissert, Charles Adam, 1878-1947.
Nov. 6, 1928.
Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.
June 18, 1913, Mar. 29, 1926, Apr. 20, 1926.
White, Lee A., b. 1886.
Dec. 5, 1923.
White, William Allen, 1868-1944.
Dec. 27, 1922.
Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.
May 30, June7, 1905 [folder 34]
Wister, Owen, 1860-1938.
Nov. 26, 1915, Feb. 14, 1919.